Guide to the Sol Gorelick Papers WAG.019
Tamiment Library and Robert F. Wagner Labor Archive
- City, State, and Federal Social Welfare Programs, 1
  - Fulton Center - Testimony Against Barbara Blum, Commissioner of the New York Department of Social Services (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - Fulton Center - Training Materials (Box 5, Folder 6)
  - Fulton Center - Transit Strike (Box 5, Folder 7)
  - Fulton Center - Unions (Box 5, Folder 8)
  - Fulton Center - United Jewish Appeal (Box 5, Folder 9)
  - Fulton Center - Utilities for Public Assistance Recipients - RESTRICTED (Box 17, Folder 39)
  - Fulton Citizens Advisory Council - Minutes (Box 5, Folder 10)
  - Fulton Client Advisory Committee/Community Advisory Committee (Box 5, Folder 11-16)
  - Fulton Client Advisory Committee/Community Advisory Committee - RESTRICTED (Box 17, Folder 40)
  - Fulton Client Advisory Committee (Includes Ad Hoc Committee for Survival) (Box 5, Folder 17)
  - Greenwood Social Service Center - Closure (Box 5, Folder 18)
  - Greenwood Welfare Center (Box 5, Folder 19)
  - Greenwood Welfare Center - Training Materials - RESTRICTED (Box 17, Folder 41)
  - Health Systems Agency of New York City (Box 5, Folder 19-22)
  - Health Systems Agency of New York City - District Board G (Box 5, Folder 23)
  - Hispanic Society of the Department of Social Services (Box 5, Folder 24)
  - Liz Holtzman (Box 5, Folder 25)
  - Housing - RESTRICTED (Box 17, Folder 42)
  - Housing and Community Development Coalition (New York City) (Box 5, Folder 26)
  - Housing Authority (New York City) (Box 5, Folder 27)
  - Housing Authority (New York City) - Advisory Committee for the Provision of Social Services in Public Housing (Box 5, Folder 28)
  - Human Resources Administration (New York City) (Box 5, Folder 29-31)
  - Human Resources Administration (New York City) - Albany Bulletin - Legislation Pertaining to Social Welfare (Box 5, Folder 32)
  - Human Resources Administration (New York City) - Address by Jule M. Sugarman, Administrator of HRA (Box 5, Folder 33)
  - Human Resources Administration (New York City) - Administration for Childhood Development (Box 5, Folder 34)
  - Human Resources Administration (New York City) - Administrator Training Program - Disciplinary Action and Hearing Procedure (Box 5, Folder 35)
  - Human Resources Administration (New York City) - Annual Report (Box 5, Folder 36)
  - Human Resources Administration (New York City) - Cabinet Meetings (Box 5, Folder 37)
  - Human Resources Administration (New York City) - Client Advisory Committee Newsletter (Box 5, Folder 38)
  - Human Resources Administration (New York City) - Community Affairs Memo (Box 5, Folder 39)
  - Human Resources Administration (New York City) - CRT and Automation (Box 5, Folder 40)
  - Human Resources Administration (New York City) - District 5 (East New York): Community Social Services, Proposed Plan (Box 5, Folder 41)
  - Human Resources Administration (New York City) - Division of Eligibility Control (Box 5, Folder 42)
  - Human Resources Administration (New York City) - Division of Medical Social Work Services (Box 5, Folder 43)
  - Human Resources Administration (New York City) - Executive Development Meetings (Box 5, Folder 44)
  - Human Resources Administration (New York City) - Field Staff Training Program (Box 5, Folder 45)
  - Human Resources Administration (New York City) - Head Start (Box 5, Folder 46)
  - Human Resources Administration (New York City) - Income Managment Center - Director's Advisory Committee (Box 5, Folder 47)
  - Human Resources Administration (New York City) - Income Managment Center - Clerical and Administrative Personnel Reports (Box 5, Folder 48)
  - Human Resources Administration (New York City) - Income Maintenance Supervisory Development and Training Program (Box 5, Folder 49)
  - Human Resources Administration (New York City) - In-Depth Study of the Human Resources Administration (Box 5, Folder 50)
  - Human Resources Administration (New York City) - Informational (Box 5, Folder 51)
  - Human Resources Administration (New York City) - Job Openings (Box 5, Folder 52)
  - Human Resources Administration (New York City) - Legislative Memos (Box 5, Folder 53)
  - Human Resources Administration (New York City) - Manpower and Career Development Agency Graduation (Box 5, Folder 54)
  - Human Resources Administration (New York City) - Memorandum regarding Gorelick's Contract (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - Human Resources Administration (New York City) - Mobile Outreach Project (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - Human Resources Administration (New York City) - Model Cities Program (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - Human Resources Administration (New York City) - Monthly Control Reports (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - Human Resources Administration (New York City) - Notice of Intent to Discontinue Public Assistance (Box 6, Folder 5)
  - Human Resources Administration (New York City) - Office of Community Services (Box 6, Folder 6)
  - Human Resources Administration (New York City) - Procedural Directives (Box 6, Folder 7)
  - Human Resources Administration (New York City) - Recruitment Flyers for Community Social Services (Box 6, Folder 8)
  - Human Resources Administration (New York City) - Regulations on the Use of Christmas Decorations (Box 6, Folder 9)
  - Human Resources Administration (New York City) - Reorganization Committee (Box 6, Folder 10)
  - Human Resources Administration (New York City) - Reorganization Plan (Box 6, Folder 11)
  - Human Resources Administration (New York City) - Report on Baltimore Department of Social Services (Box 6, Folder 12)
  - Human Resources Administration (New York City) - Reports on Detroit and Boston Departments of Social Services (Box 6, Folder 13)
  - Human Resources Administration (New York City) - Security Task Force (Box 6, Folder 14)
  - Human Resources Administration (New York City) - Shelter Allowance Policy (Box 6, Folder 15)
  - Human Resources Administration (New York City) - Staff Development Reporter Newsletter (Box 6, Folder 16)
  - Human Resources Administration (New York City) - State Demonstration Employment Programs (Box 6, Folder 17)
  - Human Resources Administration (New York City) - Summer Training Program (Box 6, Folder 18)
  - Human Resources Administration (New York City) - Supervising Clerks - RESTRICTED (Box 17, Folder 43)
  - Human Resources Administration (New York City) - Supervisory Correspondence - RESTRICTED (Box 17, Folder 44)
  - Human Resources Administration (New York City) - Supplementary Security Income Data and Information (Box 6, Folder 19)
  - Human Resources Administration (New York City) - Union Contracts and Government Regulations (Box 6, Folder 20)
  - Human Resources Administration (New York City) - "What is the HRA?" (Box 6, Folder 21)
  - Human Resources Administration (New York City) - What's on TV (Box 6, Folder 22)
  - Human Resources Administration (New York City) - Youth Service Agency (Box 6, Folder 23)
  - Intake Procedures (New York City Welfare Departments) (Box 6, Folder 24)
  - Jay Street Employment Eligibility Center (Box 6, Folder 25)
  - Job Orientation in Neighborhoods (JOIN) (Box 6, Folder 26)
  - Labor News Memorandum (Box 6, Folder 27)
  - Leave Cards (Box 6, Folder 28)
  - Leave Regulations (City of New York) (Box 6, Folder 29)
  - Legislation - New York City (Box 6, Folder 30)
  - Legislation - New York State (Box 6, Folder 31)
  - Legislation - Unidentified (Box 6, Folder 32)
  - Livingston Center (Box 6, Folder 33)
  - Model Cities (Box 6, Folder 34)
  - Municipal Civil Service Commission - Welfare Service Exams (Box 6, Folder 35)
  - NAACP - Department of Welfare (New York City) Branch (Box 6, Folder 36)
  - Nassau County Civil Service Commission (Box 6, Folder 37)
  - National Youth Administration, including Resident Project at San Marcos, Texas (Box 6, Folder 38)
  - New York State Labor Legislative Workshop (Box 6, Folder 39)
  - Office for the Aging (New York State) (Box 6, Folder 40)
  - Office of Collective Bargaining (Box 6, Folder 41)
  - Office of the Mayor (New York City) (Box 6, Folder 42)
  - Personal (Box 6, Folder 43)
  - Public Forum on Social Services - Human Resources Administration/Department of Social Services (Box 6, Folder 44)
  - Public Works Program - Job Assignments (Box 6, Folder 45)
  - Recommendations from the 1971 White House Conference on Aging (Box 6, Folder 46)
  - Republican Study Committee: Presenting Welfare 'Reform (Box 6, Folder 47)
  - Retirement, Death, and Departure Announcements - Human Resources Administration/Department of Social Services (Box 6, Folder 48)
  - Saint Nicholas Social Center (Box 6, Folder 49)
  - Social Security and Welfare Legislation (Box 6, Folder 50-52)
  - Some Effects of Turnover on the Composition of the Welfare Caseload by Richard H. Mead (Box 6, Folder 53)
  - Song and Poetry (Box 6, Folder 54)
  - Statistical Procedures (Box 6, Folder 55)
  - Study Materials for Senior Supervisor Exam (Box 6, Folder 56)
  - Stuyvesant Community Center (Box 6, Folder 57)
  - Task Force on Social Services (Box 6, Folder 58)
  - Temporary Housing Rent Commission (New York State) (Box 6, Folder 59)
  - Typescript on State of Welfare System (56 pages, Author Unidentified) (Box 6, Folder 60)
  - Workmen's Compensation Board (State of New York) (Box 6, Folder 61)
  - Work Relief Employment Project - Manual for Public Agency Employees (Box 6, Folder 62)
  - Wyckoff Center (Box 6, Folder 63)
  - Youth Board (New York City) (Box 6, Folder 64)
  - Youth Service Agency: "How the Youth Service Agency Serves the Brownsville Community" (Box 6, Folder 65)
- Labor and Unions, 2
  Sol Gorelick had a long and active involvement in public social service workers' unions that coincided with a particularly tempestuous period for labor relations with the New York City government.
  Gorelick joined the United Public Workers union upon starting work at the Brownsville Welfare Center in 1940. The UPW would be expelled from the Congress of Industrial Organizations in 1950, during the CIO's anti-Communist purges. In its wake, two unions sprang up to represent workers in New York City's Department of Welfare: the American Federation of Labor-affiliated Social Investigators Union, Local 1193 and the CIO-affiliated American Civic Employees Union, Local 371. With the merger of the AFL and CIO in 1955, these two unions came together to found the Welfare Local 371 within the American Federation of State, County and Municipal Employees, District Council 37. Gorelick served as a vice president of DC 37 in the 1960s.
  The 1960s were a period of great tension between AFSCME and the City of New York. Many caseworkers, particularly at the Brownsville Welfare Center, felt that AFSCME, DC 37 was not aggressive enough in its negotiations with the city. During a 1961 dispute between AFSCME and the city, this group petitioned the city to form a separate union. Happy to undercut AFSCME, the Department of Labor granted the request, and the Social Service Employees Union was formed. In the following years both the SSEU and Local 371 would compete for members in the Department of Welfare.
  The SSEU called a walkout in 1964, and held a strike in 1964-1965 that Local 371 joined. During this strike Gorelick was sent to jail for resisting a judge's order. The SSEU initiated a sit-in 1966 that DC 37 and the New York City Central Labor Council were eventually dragged into to protect bargaining rights. The subsequent loss of this strike, along with changes to practices in the department, led to the weakening of the SSEU. They began merger talks with Local 371 in 1968. When an agreement was reached in 1969, the Social Service Employees Union, Local 371 was formed within AFSCME, DC 37.
  Gorelick remained a member of the union until his retirement 1980, and participated in DC 37's community activism beyond that.
  This series documents Sol Gorelick's union activities during his tenure with the City of New York's social service departments. It contains a wide range of documentation, including meeting minutes, contracts, forms, pamphlets, fliers, newsletters, conference materials, and correspondence. The best represented unions are the Welfare Local 371, the Social Service Employees Union, Local 371, and their parent organization American Federation of State, County and Municipal Employees, District Council 37.
  Gorelick joined the United Public Workers union when he joined the Department of Welfare, and there is one folder of materials regarding this union. The Welfare Local 371 of AFSCME, DC 37 (1955-1969) is particularly well-represented. These materials include negotiation documentation, contracts, publications, and committee materials. There are six folders of material on the Social Service Employees Union (1961-1969), that for a time competed with Local 371 for members from the Department of Welfare. In 1969, Local 371 and the SSEU merged. The resulting union, SSEU Local 371 is also well represented. Documentation includes the local's newsletter, chapter and committee materials, and leaflets. The is also a significant amount of material form AFSCME, DC 37, the AFL-CIO-affiliated parent union of Local 371 and SSEU Local 371.
  There is small amount of additional material from other social service locals, unions outside of the social services, and peace advocacy activities in the trade union movement.
  - Ad Hoc Committee for Collective Bargaining (Box 6, Folder 66)
  - AFL-CIO (Box 6, Folder 67)
  - AFSCME (Box 6, Folder 68)
  - AFSCME (Box 7, Folder 1-3)
  - AFSCME, District Council 37 (Box 7, Folder 4-9)
  - AFSCME, District Council 37 - Contract with City of New York (Box 7, Folder 10)
  - AFSCME, District Council 37 - 1975 Layoffs (Box 7, Folder 11)
  - AFSCME, District Council 1707 (Box 7, Folder 12)
  - AFSCME, District Council 1707 - Strike (Box 7, Folder 13)
  - AFSCME - Grievance Form (Box 7, Folder 14)
  - Brooklyn Friends of the Labor Research Association (LRA) (Box 7, Folder 15)
  - CIO (Box 7, Folder 16)
  - City Employees Union, Local 237 (Box 7, Folder 17)
  - Civil Service Technical Guild (Box 7, Folder 18)
  - Committee on Union Responsibility (Box 7, Folder 19)
  - Communication Workers of America (Box 7, Folder 20)
  - Grievance Newsletter (Box 7, Folder 21)
  - Grievances - RESTRICTED (Box 17, Folder 45-46)
  - ILGWU, Local 66 - Leadership Training Institute (Box 7, Folder 22)
  - Industrial Workers of the World (Box 7, Folder 23)
  - Labor Research Association (Box 7, Folder 24)
  - Legal Services Staff Association (Box 7, Folder 25)
  - Local 112 (Maryland Social Service Workers, AFSCME) (Box 7, Folder 26)
  - Welfare Local 371 - Arbitrations (Box 7, Folder 27)
  - Welfare Local 371 - Bulletin (Box 7, Folder 28)
  - Welfare Local 371 - Chapters - Greenwood (Box 7, Folder 29)
  - Welfare Local 371 - Chapters - Supervisors (Box 7, Folder 30)
  - Welfare Local 371 - Civil Rights (Box 7, Folder 31)
  - Welfare Local 371 - Clerical-Administrative Coloring Book for City Employees (Box 7, Folder 32)
  - Welfare Local 371 - Committtee for Effective Leadership within Welfare Local 371 (Box 7, Folder 33)
  - Welfare Local 371 - Committee for Union Democracy (Box 7, Folder 34)
  - Welfare Local 371 - Committees - Grievances (Box 7, Folder 35)
  - Welfare Local 371 - Committees - Downtown Brooklyn Organizing (Box 7, Folder 36)
  - Welfare Local 371 - Committees - Fact-finding (Box 7, Folder 37)
  - Welfare Local 371 - Committees - Finance (Box 7, Folder 38)
  - Welfare Local 371 - Committees - Legislative (Box 7, Folder 39)
  - Welfare Local 371 - Committees - Membership (Box 7, Folder 40)
  - Welfare Local 371 - Constitutions (Box 7, Folder 41)
  - Welfare Local 371 - Contracts (Box 7, Folder 42)
  - Welfare Local 371 - Correspondence (Box 7, Folder 43)
  - Welfare Local 371 - Directory (Box 7, Folder 44)
  - Welfare Local 371 - Elections (Box 7, Folder 45)
  - Welfare Local 371 - Exam Protests (Box 7, Folder 46)
  - Welfare Local 371 - Executive Board (Box 7, Folder 47)
  - Welfare Local 371 - Finances (Box 7, Folder 48)
  - Welfare Local 371 - General (Box 7, Folder 49-51)
  - Welfare Local 371 - Jack Goldberg Pamphlet - A Professional Views the Union (Box 7, Folder 52)
  - Welfare Local 371 - Legislative (Box 7, Folder 53)
  - Welfare Local 371 - Letterhead (Box 7, Folder 54)
  - Welfare Local 371 - Lists of Names (Box 7, Folder 55)
  - Welfare Local 371 - Mechanics of the Job: A Guide for Caseworkers (Box 7, Folder 56)
  - Welfare Local 371 - Merger with SSEU (Box 7, Folder 57)
  - Welfare Local 371 - Negotiations (Box 7, Folder 58-60)
  - Welfare Local 371 - Notes (Box 8, Folder 1)
  - Welfare Local 371 - Organizational Newsletter (Box 8, Folder 2)
  - Welfare Local 371 - Reclassification (Box 8, Folder 3)
  - Welfare Local 371 - Resolutions (Box 8, Folder 4)
  - Welfare Local 371 - The Scene (Box 8, Folder 5)
  - Welfare Local 371 - Welfare Local 371 News (Box 8, Folder 6)
  - Welfare Local 371 - Training (Box 8, Folder 7)
  - Local 1193 - Flyer and Newsletter (Box 8, Folder 8)
  - Local 1199 - Hospital Division (Box 8, Folder 9)
  - Local 1549 (Box 8, Folder 10)
  - Municipal Labor Committee (Box 8, Folder 11)
  - National Federation of Social Service Employees (Box 8, Folder 12)
  - Negro American Labor Council (Box 8, Folder 13)
  - New York City Central Labor Council (Box 8, Folder 14)
  - New York Committee for Trade Union Action and Democracy (Box 8, Folder 15)
  - New York State AFL-CIO (Box 8, Folder 16)
  - New York Typographical Union Number 6 (Box 8, Folder 17)
  - Public Employees for Peace (Box 8, Folder 18)
  - Public Services Association (Box 8, Folder 19)
  - Salary Review Board (Box 8, Folder 20)
  - Albert Segal (Box 8, Folder 21)
  - SANE (National Committee for Sane Nuclear Policy): Trade Union Division (Box 8, Folder 22)
  - Social Service Employees Union (SSEU) (Box 8, Folder 23)
  - Social Service Employees Union (SSEU) - Community Action Committee (Box 8, Folder 24)
  - Social Service Employees Union (SSEU) - Elections (Box 8, Folder 25)
  - Social Service Employees Union (SSEU) - Health (Box 8, Folder 26)
  - Social Service Employees Union (SSEU) - Members for a Militant Caucus (Box 8, Folder 27)
  - Social Services Employees Union (SSEU) - Timetable of Operations During Strike (Boro Hall) (Box 8, Folder 28)
  - Social Services Employees Union (SSEU), Local 371 - Activists Lists (Box 8, Folder 29)
  - Social Services Employees Union (SSEU), Local 371 - Bulletin (Box 8, Folder 30)
  - Social Services Employees Union (SSEU), Local 371 - Case Aides (Box 8, Folder 31)
  - Social Services Employees Union (SSEU), Local 371 - Certification (Box 8, Folder 32)
  - Social Services Employees Union (SSEU), Local 371 - Chapters - Bureau of Public Assistance (BPA) (Box 8, Folder 33)
  - Social Services Employees Union (SSEU), Local 371 - Chapters - Caseworker Chapter (Box 8, Folder 34)
  - Social Services Employees Union (SSEU), Local 371 - Chapters - Clinton (Box 8, Folder 35)
  - Social Services Employees Union (SSEU), Local 371 - Chapters - Human Resources Administration (Box 8, Folder 36)
  - Social Services Employees Union (SSEU), Local 371 - Chapters - Shelter & Institutional Employees (Box 8, Folder 37)
  - Social Services Employees Union (SSEU), Local 371 - Chapters - Social Services Employees (Box 8, Folder 38)
  - Social Services Employees Union (SSEU), Local 371 - Chapters - Supervisors (Box 8, Folder 39)
  - Social Services Employees Union (SSEU), Local 371 - Civil Liberties Activism (Box 8, Folder 40)
  - Social Services Employees Union (SSEU), Local 371 - Committee for a New Leadership (Box 8, Folder 41)
  - Social Services Employees Union (SSEU), Local 371 - Committee for a Solid Contract (Box 8, Folder 42)
  - Social Services Employees Union (SSEU), Local 371 - Community Relations and Services Committee (Box 8, Folder 43)
  - Social Services Employees Union (SSEU), Local 371 - Earmarking Committee (Box 8, Folder 44)
  - Social Services Employees Union (SSEU), Local 371 - Election Committee (Box 8, Folder 45)
  - Social Services Employees Union (SSEU), Local 371 - Executive Committee (Box 8, Folder 46)
  - Social Services Employees Union (SSEU), Local 371 - Finance Committee (Box 8, Folder 47)
  - Social Services Employees Union (SSEU), Local 371 - Legislative and Political Action Committee (Box 8, Folder 48)
  - Social Services Employees Union (SSEU), Local 371 - Rank and File Committee (Box 8, Folder 49)
  - Social Services Employees Union (SSEU), Local 371 - Reorganization and Workload Committee (Box 8, Folder 50)
  - Social Services Employees Union (SSEU), Local 371 - Service Committee (Box 8, Folder 51)
  - Social Services Employees Union (SSEU), Local 371 - Special Executive Committee (Box 8, Folder 52)
  - Social Services Employees Union (SSEU), Local 371 - Collective Bargaining Committee (Box 8, Folder 53)
  - Social Services Employees Union (SSEU), Local 371 - Constitutions (Box 8, Folder 54)
  - Social Services Employees Union (SSEU), Local 371 - Contracts (Box 8, Folder 55)
  - Social Services Employees Union (SSEU), Local 371 - Correspondence (Box 8, Folder 56)
  - Social Services Employees Union (SSEU), Local 371 - Delegates (to District Council 37) and Trustee Elections (Box 8, Folder 57)
  - Social Services Employees Union (SSEU), Local 371 - Delegates Assembly (Box 8, Folder 58)
  - Social Services Employees Union (SSEU), Local 371 - Educational Fund (Box 8, Folder 59)
  - Social Services Employees Union (SSEU), Local 371 - Elections (Box 8, Folder 60)
  - Social Services Employees Union (SSEU), Local 371 - Frank Barbaro Endorsement (Box 8, Folder 61)
  - Social Services Employees Union (SSEU), Local 371 - General (Box 8, Folder 62)
  - Social Services Employees Union (SSEU), Local 371 - Leaflets and Circulars (Box 8, Folder 63)
  - Social Services Employees Union (SSEU), Local 371 - Grievance Board - RESTRICTED (Box 17, Folder 47)
  - Social Services Employees Union (SSEU), Local 371 - Jurisdiction List (Box 8, Folder 64)
  - Social Services Employees Union (SSEU), Local 371 - Members for a Better Union (Box 8, Folder 65)
  - Social Services Employees Union (SSEU), Local 371 - Membership Counts (Box 8, Folder 66)
  - Social Services Employees Union (SSEU), Local 371 - Memos to Gorelick (Box 8, Folder 67)
  - Social Services Employees Union (SSEU), Local 371 - News Clippings (Box 8, Folder 68)
  - Social Services Employees Union (SSEU), Local 371 - Notes (Box 8, Folder 69)
  - Social Services Employees Union (SSEU), Local 371 - New York State AFL-CIO (Box 8, Folder 70)
  - Social Services Employees Union (SSEU), Local 371 - Organizational Newsletter (Box 8, Folder 71-73)
  - Social Services Employees Union (SSEU), Local 371 - Position Papers (Box 8, Folder 74)
  - Social Services Employees Union (SSEU), Local 371 - "Purchase Power," Consumer Benefit Plans (Box 8, Folder 75)
  - Social Services Employees Union (SSEU), Local 371 - Robert S. Pfefferman, From Seperation to Title XX: The Worker's Story (Box 8, Folder 76)
  - Social Services Employees Union (SSEU), Local 371 - Training (Box 8, Folder 77)
  - Social Services Employees Union (SSEU), Local 371 - Union Funds-misappropriation Charges (Box 8, Folder 78)
  - Social Services Employees Union (SSEU), Local 371 - Welfare Fund (Box 8, Folder 79)
  - Social Services Employees Union (SSEU), Local 371 - Work Stoppage (Box 8, Folder 80)
  - Strike (Box 8, Folder 81-82)
  - Strikes - Social Workers, General (Box 9, Folder 1)
  - William Tambeau - RESTRICTED (Box 18, Folder 2)
  - Pauline Thornton (Box 9, Folder 2)
  - Trade Unionists for Peace (Box 9, Folder 3)
  - Transport Workers Union: Contract Information (Box 9, Folder 4)
  - United Farm Workers (Box 9, Folder 5)
  - United Public Workers (UPW) and United Public Workers of America (UPWOA) (Box 9, Folder 6)
  - One by One, United WREP Workers Newsletter (Box 9, Folder 7)
  - Welfare Workers for Peace (Box 9, Folder 8)